Another really great way to end your practices with a spinal twist is one of my personal favorites, it feels really, really good.
So Willie is going to lift this leg up for me. Just bring his knee up into his chest. He's going to take his arms out to the sides in a T. Good.
He's going to bring his knee across his chest and over to the side.
Now as a partner, your job is to keep your partner's shoulder leveled.
And the first thing I'm going to do is get familiar with his breath so that I can move with his breath.
I'm going to ask him to inhale in and as he exhales, I'm just going to give gentle pressure to his shoulder and pull his hip long to lengthen out through that side body.
On his next inhale I'm going to release and then on his exhale I'm going to press his hip over.
And be sure to ask your partner when to stop.
So you tell me when.
Keep going, keep going, it feels really good.
So then again moving with your partner's breath inhaling and exhaling.
You might find each time he exhales he's able to come into it just a little bit deeper as he opens up through his side body just a little bit more.
Again this is a really delicious pose, it feels really good.